Oh, is that it?
Welcome.
Hey. - Hey.
Yoo-hoo.
Bottom.
All right.
Ah, it's done.
Good evening.
Thank you.
And now, without further ado...
To all the Sakura Sakura channel viewers.
Good evening.
I'm Tamura Hano.
I'm Megumi Yamazaki.
Hey, look, look, look.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I am Tamura Hano.
I am Mizuho Hanyu.
I am Arina Mori.
I am Sayuki Ikeo.
I am Mui Ohno.
I am Seino,
I'm Sakura P or 46!
Wow!
Good evening!
This is Sakura Saka Channel's first live broadcast,
Tonight, we'll be broadcasting from the SakuraSaka46 exhibition, Shinsekai, at the Roppongi Museum in Tokyo.
Sakura-saka46 exhibition, Shinsekai, which is currently being held at the Roppongi Museum in Tokyo.
Hey there!
Welcome!Welcome!
Welcome! Do some of you look familiar? I don't know.
I remember you.
Where am I?
Hey.
Yes.
Uh, at the venue, chapter 5, section 10,
The tree behind me where I'm sitting here,
The tree behind you is the actual tree that was used for the Samidarea artwork shoot at the Force.
You can see the base of the tree.
It's nostalgic.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing, isn't it? I miss it.
Samina Leo, you took this.
You took it.
I actually drank it, so I miss it.
It brings back memories.
He kept it in there.
He was eating it while writing it down in the warehouse.
It's like he was eating it while writing it down. Yeah.
He had really cool makeup.
He also liked makeup.
He made it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The flowers are cute.
You know, I'm not scared. Beyond the flowers.
Flowers, right?
A room.
Room?
Our room.In our room.
Office room? In our room, in our office.
In our office.
We have flowers in our room.
Flowers stay here.
Yeah, flowers in the room.
I loved you in that outfit.
I know.
She was so cute.
Misaka is delivering the goods right now.
I'll read the comments as I go.
Are you getting anything? Are you getting any comments or anything?
What do you think? I want to see it... and I don't know if I can do it.
I can hear your voice, even your chest.
I'm talking... ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm on the move in a new world.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I got it.
Hello.
Oh, shoes.
Which one's the home team?
Look at this.
Sandals.
Let me show you my sandals.
I'm wearing sandals.
Yay. I'm like a youth.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go.That's right.
Glimpse, glimpse, glimpse.
Wow!
It's too bright.
Just for a minute.
New world.
A little bit of who.
Someone's going to tell me.
Hey, did you really think...? I'm curious about this.
No, no, no, no.
There's a reason.
You sure? I told you.
Can I?
Can I say it?
I chose "Maruse" because the world is round.
I see.
It's not round.
That's correct.
The world is round, and I want everyone in the world to be like that.
I thought it was round.
Not yet.
I want everyone to be in a circle, as if we are all together.
Peace, peace.
I made it round. Rounded. Lovely. It has a meaning. Oh, .... Is that it?
Suzuki is a cat too!
That's a cat!That's a cat!
They're all so thoughtful.
There's so much personality.
Is the picture quality bad? I don't know, maybe.
It's too bright in here.
You're gonna get it? Let's get out of here.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Let's go!
Goods coming in!
It's so spacious!
Goods! Goods! Goods!
Goods! Goods!
We're doing great!
Goods! We're doing great!
You have this, don't you, Mr. Kabu?
I have it! It's so cute! It's really fashionable, isn't it?
I bought some socks too. Oh, that's right.
Socks. The fabric was really good.
It's really good. Very nice. They are thick, aren't they? Yes, yes, yes.
What did you buy, Honachan? I bought that. A key chain. Key chain.
Key chain.
What are you doing?
It's turning white.
Oh, that's right.
It's in stock.
It was in stock.
Yes, everyone loves it.Yes, we all love it.
Finally, I got it today.
Yes, you bought it. Just now.
You did it.
The key ring.
Everyone bought it, right?
Everyone.
Everyone's wearing them.
Ta-da! Like this.
The key visual of the members' new world.
Tenchan. The key visual of now. Now. Now. It's so crazy.
This is the key visual that Tei-chan is working on.
This is it.
This is the one that Runa-chan says she's in charge of.
I'm in charge of this.
How was the shoot? How was the shoot?
It's true.
It was something, but..,
Wait a minute, I picked a weird one.
Are you okay?
I'm going to combine the costumes from the first to the fourth album with the costumes for the jackets, and have three special outfits made, just for the three of us.
It's a little hard to see here. Can I put them over there?
It's fine.
I'm going to wash the image quality.
You know, everyone says "quality wash", right?
This is it, this is it.
Can you see this?
See?
Cue visuals of this new world.
That's right. New world cue visual.Right. New World cue visual.
Special thanks to Mr. Oslin, he made it for me.
Really.
This one.
It's really nice, isn't it? The actual costumes are on display.
Yes, it's on display.
That's right, Sori.
That's real.
That's Ten-chan's hand.
She's touching your hand.
She's holding hands with Ten.
I'm holding hands with Ten-chan.
There are a lot of goodies here.
These flowers.
Real flowers.
Oh, yeah.
They were real.
Rose?
Stick it in like an ikebana.
Yes, a rose... a rose-colored rose? Rose! Rose! Rose of laughter.
Oh, I didn't know that.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's a new world.
You're Rose, aren't you Rose?
I want a croissant.
I'd love to.
They're good again, aren't they?
I'm going back to where we were.I'm going to go back... to the place we were just talking about.
I think I'm gonna be a little better going out.
I'm gonna be okay going out.
I wonder if it's gonna be okay to go out.
It's a new world, though.
It's a different time and space.
I see.
Hey, guys, look.
Look at me.
Squeeze time!
Suddenly...
Then take off your shoes.
Thank you, Honokyan.
Okay!
Not at all.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We can all get on the screen now.
Let's sit down.
Welcome back, everybody.
Shall we? Okay, we've switched seats.
I hope it's all right. I hope it's all right.
I hope I'm not too drunk.
I'll adjust the angle for you guys.
I'll adjust the angle.
Thank you.
I'd like you to try sitting down, but you're so cute... Excuse me.
Excuse me.Excuse me, sir.
Keep coming forward.
You're right, it hasn't changed.
I think I'll stay here.
I rotated.
Let's see...
So...
Oh, yeah.
Now the live delivery, oh, someone's not on the screen. Oh, the manager.
He was drinking water.
Well, this is the second time we've done a live stream, how about you guys? Is this your first time?
It's my first time.
It's my second time,
I was watching.
You did, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Miki was in the heat, too. I want to know about Miki, too. How was it?
She seemed to be having fun.
Oh, yeah, of course. It's because of my age.
That's right.
Let's do it again in paradise.
Let's do it again.
Yes, let's do it again. So tonight, I would like to talk about a lot of things while responding to your comments.
Yes, I will.
Yay.
So, first of all, a mouthful! I'm going to start right away,
Let me do it.
7 mime singles. My initial desire is...7 Mime Singles - First Time Desire
to be released on October 18!
Yay!
Thank you!
So, the first round of application for Meet & Greet
The first application period ended at 2:00 p.m. today, I think.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not.
I wonder if it was easy or not. I wonder if it was easy. I wonder if it was easy. I'll be waiting.
How's the fun?
Are they talking?
I wonder if they're coming.
Is this it?
But what is it?
Um, what is it?
Samira Leo? From,
Samira Leo Sakuragetsu, with a day off at the start,
The first letter of the name is "S".
What!
Wow! That's amazing!
I didn't notice.
Because it's cherry blossoms?
What!
With each other?
Oh! Is that what you mean?
That's scary!
Sad!
Scary!
I wonder if S has some kind of circle.
That's great.
It sure is.I'm sure.
I've noticed
New discovery
Interesting
Only in the world
But what's with the kanji characters?
That's right.
Science fiction...
Since then?
That's for sure.
Is there anything else left?
Well, I'm half-convinced, half-doubtful, and half-doubtful. How many more songs were there? Um, half a doubt...
Oh, half a doubt.
Sure, sure.
There have been a lot of cool songs so far, haven't there?
Yes, they are.
But you'll see what happens.
So..,
Today, they announced.
Hamdatebook!
Yay!
On December 7, my first photo book will be released!
Today's announcement?
I'm so happy.
I love the black jacket.
I like the black jacket the best.I like it best.
Red Yome Nails. I love it already.
You guys are really the best. Tomorrow was that.
Showroom? We have a showroom at 9:00 p.m,
I have to see it. I have to see it.
What do you have for me? Something we can talk about here?
Certainly. It's your first time.
But really...
I've had a lot of pictures taken,
I had a lot of pictures taken,
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hanmari has to see it.
Congratulations to everyone! I'm so excited!
She said, "I'm so happy for you!
She was so cute.
They were so lovely.
I guess you could call it an advance cut.
That cut that Rui mentioned earlier is the most popular among the members.
I'm so happy. Did everyone see it?
They are all healthy, aren't they?
Thank you very much.
I also watched the announcement video.
I saw it!
I'm looking forward to hearing everyone's comments.
Yes, I am. Actually.
Yes, I am. Thank you very much.
Enjoy.
I made a reservation.
There was a comment asking me to show you Sen-chan's T-shirt.
Sen-chan's T-shirt is cute.Sen-chan's T-shirt is cute.
Cute heart.
Thump, thump, thump.
I think everyone is having so much fun.
I'm sure they are.
I think everyone is really looking forward to it,
So please enjoy.
So, Mr. Habu,
Yes.
It's the last one on Anniversary Rain.
That's right.
Yay.
With Sakurazaka.
Yes, on November 25th and 26th.
At Dzomani Stadium.
Sakurazaka Hosonori Shikku Sadotsu Third Year Anime Fantasy Live will be held.
Yay. Is it the first day of that?
Yes, it's going to be held on the 25th.
Is this a surprise?
No, I'm serious.
I was very serious.
The day of the announcement.
The day HAB's graduation is announced.
I think it was announced on the blog on the day that HAB's graduation was announced.
I think it was announced on the blog.
I knew that they were going to make the announcement on that day
I knew it was going to be announced on that day.
I was with Yui at the time.
I was with Yui at the time, and we were talking about how to cause radio interference.
I was saying,I said,
I couldn't get it up.
LOL.
I'm glad.
He said he would definitely go.
Is it cold?
It's cold.
You should get warm.
Is it a sea breeze?
I heard it's cold.
It seems to be.
It's a bit like a stadium.
I guess only three of us have cars.
It's a part-time job.
I thought you liked Rei-chan.
Thank you.
It's after the release of the seventh single, right?
That, too.
October?
I see. We are also very excited. October 18. I see.
We are also very excited.
I don't know what's going to happen.
You said you're going to burn the hubby.
That's right.
I'm going to burn myself too.
It's a big scale, isn't it?
Normally, for the first time.Usually for the first time.
It's in a studio.
So, to be honest, I have some anxiety about it,
I'm looking forward to having many people come and see the show,
So we are looking forward to seeing you.
So we are looking forward to seeing you,
Let's see..,
Oh, I like this one, it's green. Oh, I see. Oh, I see. It's rare today, isn't it?
It's cute.
Don't show it to me like that.
You're cute.
Thank you very much.
So, everyone, this is a YouTube broadcast from Sakurazaka Channel, and I was wondering if you would be interested in doing what we all want to do.
I've been asked to make a video for youtube.
Is there anything you guys want to do? Do you have a lot of things?
Yes? But I was just talking about the hot springs club.
I like you! You don't know that yet? You don't know that I like the Hot Springs Club? Hot Springs Club.
I see.
I love hot springs.
You love hot springs.
All four of them.
You mean?
Homu Tamura, Yurina Matsuda, Yui Takemoto and me
We have a group called "Onsen Doukai".
That's right.
We have a group, but we haven't been able to go anywhere.
We haven't.
We went once.
I mean, I went to MV.
I went on campus.I went to college.
He went to college.
That's why he's teaming up with you.
I want to go.
I'd like to make that happen.
So you don't have it yet?
I would like to go, but it's hard to fit it into everyone's schedule,
I wish I could go on YouTube.
It's nowhere to be found, as it is.
I made it happen with my first make-up artist,
She said you were so happy.
Me?
Yeah, Mizuki was really supportive.
I was really happy. It was the first time I went alone.
I heard it was next time. First time at a sushi bar?
I've never been alone.
I've never gone alone.
That's for sure.
I've been to a thrift store before.
Today, I bought this Anpanman.
It's cute.
At Fisher's. Cute. It's nice. I wore it with everyone else. Today, well, I got the album I bought. As expected.
Cute.
It's nice.
I'd like to wear it with everyone.
For sure. Can I have them choose?
You can have them choose.
Sure.
I'd like to try a felt sometime.
Oh, I'd love to do that!Oh, I want to do that!
Can I have it written down?
Oh, that one.
That one.
Please try it on.
I'm so happy. I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
I don't know, I want to go to so many places,
I want to go to a lot of places, and there are places I want to go,
I'm still working on the YouTube project, so I'll be working on it with the members.
So I've been working with the members quite a bit,
I'm surprised that I've been able to do it with the members,
I'm surprised, but I'd like to do some things with the members.
What about chocolate?
Chocolate?
Yes, we should do a chocolate project for Valentine's Day, right?
That's great!
I'd love to know what you recommend.
I even took pictures.
You even did that?
Like a simulation?
Is that okay?
No, she'll be happy.
Not with chocolate, but in general.
Only with chocolate. I made a funny voice. I want you to make me a lot of love, not just with chocolate, but with a lot of people. Only with chocolate.
I made a strange voice.
Only with chocolate.
Do you have any books?
What? But the book is published by Monstergate.Eh? Ah, but the book is published by Monstelludo.
Ah.
I want to do it in Yingli Xinyi.
Where are you going?
What do you guys want to see?
Sure thing.
I have some places I want to go.
Oh, really?
I forgot.
Something nice?
Yes. It has a Japanese touch to it, and I'd like to propose it.
I want to go in the river.
Den-chan has been saying she wants to go in the cold river.
I want to go in the cold river.
What do you want to see?
Sure, what do you want to see?
Makeup!
Bena did it, didn't she?
I'd like to see some writing on it.
Travel plans.
Prevention?
I like it.
How's that?
I don't know.
Chocolate.
I'm looking forward to the chocolate project.
But I want someone to come to Kagoshima.
I want to say! I want to say! Yes! What are you going to do about the real new choco project? But I want someone to come to Kagoshima.
Yes! I want to say! Yes!What? ! I want to say it! Yes!
Yes! I'll be there!
Then, I'll be waiting for Risa.
I'll be there, Sensei!
You're coming, right?
I've been craving rice cakes.
I've been saying that.
Ria introduced it.
She introduced it on Bacubi, and it's rice cakes.
I don't know why.
They're soft. I'm sure you like it.
I think Nena-chan would like it too.
That's right, that's right.
They're together downstairs.
That's right.
Very mochi.
Much mochi.
Oh, my gosh.
Delicious.
It's a sweet style.
Sweet style. Yes, it is. I have to do it. You've been fulfilling your obligations, haven't you?
Oh, yes.
Youth?
It was great.
It was. How was it?
It was great! I want to go back and watch it again on YouTube.
Everyone's hair is shiny.Everyone's hair is shaggy too.
Oh, yeah. I got a cold face.
I was in.
Yes, I was in it.
It was a lot of fun.
It's true, isn't it? With everyone,
Before Honne-san graduates,
I want to go on a trip with everyone.
I want to go.
All together.
That's cool.
I'll go all-in.
All the way.
It's cool.
I'll carry the luggage.
Honne, what should I do?
I can't give it to you. I'm going to use the hair dryer.
I'm going to change.
Can I take a bath?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're a baby again.
I don't know which is better.
A bath.
That's funny.
I want to do a surprise.
I want to.
I love working when people are surprised.
I love it when you're surprised.
No, I understand.No, I know.
I'd like to surprise you.
Why do you have to have that butt?
Oh, that's nice.
So, are all of you guys here subscribers?
24,000 subscribers?
What, right now?
No?
Oh, yeah!
They're watching.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Is it 9:30 right now? What is he doing?
What are they doing?
Having dinner?
Are they eating?
You're thinking of watching it while eating, aren't you?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I heard you got caramelized.
Did you get caramelized?
I don't think so.
Maybe not.
That's good, that's good.
I want to be fucked.
I'm sorry.
I was just getting hungry.
I know it's not my place to come out here and do this, but...
Okay, here we go.
Did you get caramelized? Ehhhh!
I can't!No!
What does it mean?
It's a thing that was born out of the introduction of chocolate.
In the chocolate.
The almonds, or nuts, in the chocolate
Caramelized.
It's caramelized.
You're going to coat it? It's like...
Oh, it's so deep. Don't get too deep.
It shouldn't be that deep.
You're right.
If you put shrimp on it...
That's right.
Anyway, it's cute.
I mean, cute.
Well, someone's still working.
How are you looking?
Good work.
You put it in your pocket.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's what you mean?
That's cute.
Hey, guys.
So here's the thing.
I've got some plans for YouTube in the future.
I also have a plan for the future.
I'm sorry...
I don't know what I'm allowed to say.
Can I tell people?
You can say this.You can say this.
Ino and Hika-chan also go where they want.
We will go to the place we love.
Let's go there.
You go somewhere.
Den-chan, you know.
I went to Kusatsu Onsen.
Wow.
Kusatsu Onsen.
In Gunma.
I was allowed to go there.
Rika-chan's hometown together. That's right.
I wanted to go there.
I saw the pictures. It's so beautiful.
Did you see it?
I did. I did.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I'll show you later.
I'll get it to you.
Look forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I've been lonely.
I knew it.
Alone.
You're usually alone, aren't you?
Almost.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
Looking forward to it.Enjoy!
Enjoy.
More and more comments that I really read to the end.
Eh, I'm glad.
I don't have another one of these.
That's right.
Well, but not at all.
I'll go spin it a bit then.
They're all cute.
Thanks over here, too.
Let's see...
Oh, if you do that one time...
I'd like to ask you something, Buddy's.
What do you want to ask me, Buddy's?
Oh, anything... anything.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
What do you think?
There's nothing but beautiful women here.
Well, that's very kind of you.
I knew it.
You put your feet up?
Enjoy.
Ouch.
It hurts.
Really enjoy.
Ouch.
What's wrong?
Here it comes!Here it comes!
I'm so happy!
Something weird fell out.
There?
He wants me to skydive.
How's that sound?
Hey, guys.
What do you think?
Bungee jumping?
I can't do it. I can't do it.
You did it, but it wasn't great? That's great. That's great.
Wasn't it great?
Are you glad you did it?
I'm glad I did it.
What would you do if you were asked to do it again?
Maybe I could polish it up.
It would feel good.
It was really bad.
And it was a recent swing.
That's right.
I was given a will of my own. It was a spawn, wasn't it? Yes, it was. It was a squeeze monster.
That was scary.
I don't think I'll ever be a Squeezeblanc.
What about being blown out of the sky?
I'd rather do Squeeze One Blanc.
I know there are people who say, "I'd rather be blown out of the sky.
No, I don't.
Yes, there are.
I'll turn into a bird.
I'll turn into a bird, won't I?I'll be a bird I'll be a bird I'll be a bird
I'm gonna be a bird.
Wow!
That's really fast.
That was fast.
She wants to hear about Arencia.
Oh, that's nice. It was fun.
It was fun. It was fun. It was fun.
It was fun.
What do you remember most?
What? Yes, yes...
You know, the guy who ate the green grass.
At the restaurant, with the garlic.
Where did you eat?
The long one?
He ate it.
He said it was good.
How many days?
We were the last to eat together.
Some people are leaving at night.
That's right. The day it rained.
The day it rained. Oh, really?
Oh, ho!
What?
There it is.
Well, you can all imagine.
I wonder what it is.
That was delicious.
That was delicious.That was delicious.
Oh, yeah.
I looked it up, but I forgot.
Uh, I'm listening.
I'm listening.
I wonder.
You like garlic?
Something about the first one I heard, too.
Oh, yeah.
It was in the back left corner.
What? It was in the back left corner.
Turn to the side.
Wasn't he trying too hard?
It was in the back left.
It was delicious.
That's it, isn't it?
I can't wait to go back.
Is there a country you want to go to?
I'd love to go back. Do you have a country you'd like to go to? Oh, yeah, countries we want to go to.
I'm sure there are. I'm sure everyone does.
I want to go to England.
Wow, England?
I'd love to go.
What's there to do?
I don't know, like touring castles and stuff.
I want to visit castles.
I want to go so much.I want to go so badly.
That's really all I want to do, just to see the buildings and stuff,
I really don't mind just seeing the buildings and stuff. There are still many places in France that I would like to visit,
I want to go to all the pastry shops,
Yes, that's right.
Yes, that's for sure.
What about you guys?
Where do you want to go?
The Philippines.
Oh! I want to go!
I want to go. I want to go.
What's there? What's there?
What was it? But I also want to try the food,
Mm-hm.
I'd like to do some shopping.
Oh, I don't know.
I need to buy some school supplies.
Sure, sure.
I love it.
An Australian Princess.
That's nice.
It's really fast, isn't it?
It's so early.
They're going on a world tour.
It would be cool if they could do that. It's so fast. It's so fast. They're going on a world tour.
It would be cool if we could do that.
I want to go to Singapore, Germany, Basnalia, and Germany.
Finando.Finand.
Canada! I want to go!
I'd love to go to Canada.
I want to go to Italy, too.
Italy is nice.
Or Spain.
Indeed.
The world is a big place. It's got a big atmosphere.
It's so big.
He said wink, wink, wink. Who can wink?
Yes, go!
Go!
BACCUUNE
Wink, wink, wink.
He says you're cute, right?
What's "Merci"?
Melshi! You were on a roll, weren't you?
Sakurazaka-chan, you're looking at the French brochure.
But actually, we all did that, didn't we? Yes, we all did. Rena made it for us.
What? Not at all. I didn't talk to her.
No, I'm not talking to you.
Don't worry, I'll show you two.
Hey.
Do you want to get up?
Sure, sure.
Cough, cough, cough.
Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn.
Turn, turn, turn, how do you turn?
Circle.Round.
Behind you, Ana-chan.
That's cute.
Yeah, it's cute.
Hey, hey, hey! Behind you!
Oh, you're so cute!
As usual, as usual.
Let's see.
Bon chu.
And when Ten-chan greeted people in different countries, Ten-chan and Marina-chan learned and studied the languages of those countries...
Because in Malaysia, I used to speak French...
I couldn't help it!
You've got Sumimikomi!
Your pronunciation was really good!
She was really good. You were really good.
I still remember.
I'll tell you something.
That's what you are doing.
Oh my god!
Thank you for coming.
I'm sure.
Do you think she got the message?
I hope so.
You're a little shy.
What did you say? Shameful. What did you say? Shameful.
Malaysia.
That was fast.
There's a guy who wants to be a stock girl.
Okay, I'll meet you at Shinsekai.
I gotta go! I gotta go! I gotta go!We gotta go! We gotta go! I have to go!
Shinsekai will be over soon, right?
Oh no.
Until October 29th?
Is that so?
Until the 29th.
That's right, everyone.
Something changed today.
What was that? Where was it?
The seventh one, the approval sign.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I was working on a new Orsen,
Did anyone find it?
The day after tomorrow, Kose-san. The day after tomorrow. The day after tomorrow, Shinsekai will be renewed.
Yay!
Is that possible?
Is there?
First of all, the costumes will be renewed.
It's good, right?
Next, music video material has been added.
Cool.
What's that?
What's the new one?
The new one?
Is it a new one?
Is it a secret?
Is he going to show us what music video it's from?
Don't tell me.
Is this mine?Was this mine?
It's a woman's.
I've seen it.
I'll get to it when I learn a few things.
You're kidding.
I'm glad.
I want you to look at every inch of it.
I really do.
I've been told by fans that they didn't see it.
There were some exhibits that I didn't see.
They said, "Oh, there's something here.
I'm finding it amazing.
I want you to see that.
I want you to look at every inch of it.
Even down to the bottom.
I don't know, some fan told me that it was something that made me six inches taller.
It's in there somewhere, that's what it is.
He said it somewhere.
Fifteen centimeters? I'm 5'5", so let me see if I can find it.
Is it in the file?
It says "15 cm" somewhere.
It's very realistic. It's real. I have it right here on display.
It's somewhere in there.
No, no, no, no, no. I can carry it.
I want to go. I'm glad.
I'm glad.
He said he'll go from Shikaga. I'm happy. I'm glad. He said he'll go next time. Heh~.
I'll go next time.
I'm so glad.
I hope you'll extend it.I would like to see it extended.
Yes, that's right. But when I first heard about it, I thought it was really long.
Oh, I thought so.
A long time.
Even if it is.
Indeed.
Hurry up and get here, guys.
Really.
Come on.
Zodora.
Zodora. Zodora. Zodora. Ah, materials. What? - It's true. It's true!
Hey, Loud.
Materials.
There will be two additional music video materials
What's coming up.
Let's see
enjoy!
What's not there?
Let's make hearts together
I want to make hearts.
Wait, the position's changed.
Wait, everyone's changed.
I think it's like this.
I've changed my position.
Ready.
Casheer.
Heart?Heart?
OK.
It was a heart.
That's all, it was hearts.
LOL.
Why are you laughing?
The last day. Thank you.
The last day.
You have to reserve tickets there too, right?
Yes.
What did you eat, Kaguya? When you came.
I want to hear. I want to hear.
You ate everything, right?
I had a drift ball float.
Oh, really?
I love the two-color curry.
What was that? What was it?
The two-color curry for the rest of my life.
I had to say something about this for the press conference.
So, um, I memorized the recommendation.
Nagareitama Nisei Nicolor Curry.
I said it.
Nissei Nissei Curry.
That's good.
That one is spicy, right?
If you like spicy, you probably, you probably like it.
But not that much,
Well, it depends on your taste buds.Well, it depends on your taste buds.
It's not too spicy, but it's still spicy.
It's so spicy that it's spicy, isn't it?
Sorry, sorry.
I heard you ate a hamburger.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's good.
Um, Hanina-chan's flag?
You two coasters!
That's right.
Ham's coaster.
It was cute, wasn't it?
Well, at first I was asked to draw it in black and white,
I thought, "Oh, black and white means panda.
I didn't draw that.
I did.
But did you notice that? He's posing as a cherry blossom.
I noticed.
I moved it with my finger.
I worked hard on this.
Looking at my fingers.
While drawing it myself.
Look at it in Kansai dialect.
Kansai dialect? Look at it. Kansai dialect?
Are you guys talking in Kansai dialect too?
What do you have to say about coasters, Hanyu, just in Kansai dialect? I'll tell you a story.
Coasters, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Under the apple headphones.
Underneath. Oh! I do.Down there. Oh! I'm in.
Oh, no.
They were all food coasters,
I wanted to make them all hoods.
I wanted to do it, you know?
I don't even know what arasin is.
They're all potatoes with apple headphones.
Oh, that's nice.
I don't know.
Her hair is like Sakurazaka's, with leaves.
He's wearing his hair as a leaf.
I did the course target and got a coaster.
I'm so happy. I went to the house and got a coaster. I'm happy. I got a coaster. I am happy. I went to the house and got a coaster. I am happy.
I got a coaster.
Which Kagoshima dialect?
My favorite Kagoshima dialect.
I love the Kagoshima dialect.
It is cute.
It's cute.
I've forgotten it.
You have forgotten?
The Kagoshima dialect is cute.
I've forgotten the Kagoshima dialect. I've already forgotten it. Kagoshima. Kagoshima dialect.
We have forgotten it. I forgot it.
So, let's speak only to each other. Let's talk to each other with the same language.
Yes.
Let's use the same language.
Okay.All right.
All right. It's okay. All right.
Let's take this time and do a little bit.
Just a little bit.
I'm glad.
It's Kansai dialect, isn't it?
Indeed.
Shall I introduce you?
Really stylish.
What's wrong, Lena?
Don't say such terrible things.
She's cute, isn't she?
Meow.
How did you like it?
I knew she's cute. I wrote that I think it's really cute.
I don't know.
It's cute.
Like the point of making the eyes droopy.
There's a point like that.
If you look closely.
It's amazing.
Amazing, isn't it? Hey, Mr. Nina. It's thin. Amazing, isn't it? Thin.
Hey, hey, hey.
She's cute.
There's a little more, so there's a little more.
Thank you.
Thank you. I'm glad.Thank you. Glad to hear it.
The double is amazing too.
It's kind of, you know, cute.
And the lower eyelid is double, isn't it?
Double eyelids, too.
It also has double folds.
It's cute. She's cute. Her legs are like knitwear. Aren't they the two? There are 10 of them.
They're cute. Their feet are like knitwear, too.
I know, it's hard to do feet.
They're wearing boots.
I should have made her wear boots.
I'm Havry.
Havry.
Yes, I'm Havry. That's great.
Havubri is laughing at me for handing them out.
I'm handing it out.
It's cute.
If you buy one of these, it comes with it, right?
It comes close.
Aren't you asking for two too many?
No, I don't think so.
I'm afraid I'll think, "Don't go downstairs.
That's true. You'll get wet.
That's cute.
You know the gate.
Hey, Tamego, where are you going?
Ah!
Who's there?
Who's there?Who's there?
Tamego.
Rizmo.
Yeah. He'll cry as soon as I say this. I'm going to eat. Want some? Mizuho.
As soon as I said this, she went home.
So cute.
Mizuho-chan.
Just living with that kind of teasing from the hubs, and seeing him do it to you sometimes,
I love that. I watch it.
Fuyuka-san, right?
Fuyuka-san, too.
Fuyu-chan, will you be my hubby's girl?
Really?
You're tough.
She's tough.
Tough.
Fuuka, you're really funny.
You're really funny.
I love her.
She's really funny.
Really funny.
I really love it.
I don't like adults.
Adults, no.
Do you have any questions?Do you have any questions?
Accepted.
We are accepting questions.
You have a question?
Okay, that's fine. It's difficult.
Do you have a question?
Yes, I did.
You're the guy who said, "Yes, I was.
The one that said, "Are you watching the members?
I wonder if he's looking at the members.
Certainly.
But today, Hikaru said he'll watch.
Oh!
There he is!
You're glowing.
Garu is going, isn't he?
Certainly.
Wait a minute.
Details right away.
Saturday, September 30, Girls Award 2023
Autumn Winter.
Sakurazaka 46 will be performing live.
It's next week.
Thank you very much.
You performed on the live stage at Spring Summer as well.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you think you can get together with us, or are there any party people?
I don't know.I don't know.
Do you think people will come?
I'm also a model.
Yes, I am.
We have members like that.
Please come.
Hikaru, let's get married.
What do you think? I've been told.
Oh, I thought you said that.
I wonder if she'll comment on it.
Oh, Garoua said she'll go.
Well, thank you.
I'll be waiting.
I'll be there.
Thank you.
Yes, you are. Because that's what I'm talking about.
Like an event where you can meet Mr. HAB.
Oh, that's right.
It's going to happen more and more.
You must come, it's true.
That's right.
We'll be waiting for you.
Have you had dinner yet?
I haven't eaten yet.
What would you like?
Certainly.
Streaming eggs.
Two meals of curry.
I ateI ate.
You didn't eat. I didn't eat. I want to eat.
I want to eat.
I want to eat curry.
Sure you do.
Do you usually cook? Everyone.
Hey.
Oh, I see. Yes, I do.
That's right.
It's still going on.
It's still going on. Ei-chan cooks. Oh, you do? You mentioned it. That's right. That's right. It's still going on. Thirteen times.
Hei, you cook.
Oh, you do?
He did say that, didn't he?
And it's pretty musical.
What do you cook?
Anything.
Even make sweets?
But I don't make sweets, like cheesecake,
And I've never made it before.
It's really amazing.
That's amazing. Wait, it's amazing. No, this is...
It's amazing.
It's good.
Bolognese.
I want some Bolognese.
Pasta.Pasta.
It's delicious.
Did you make the bread?
Yes, I made bread.
You made bread? Yes, I made bread. Yes, I made bread. I made bread. Wow! That's amazing.
I like it too much. A different flavor.
What? What?
A different taste.
Different taste. I made bread.
Surprised? It tastes different.
No, it was in the comments. I really made it.
But, you know, bread takes a long time to ferment.
I made pizza for a while too.
You have to put something down.
Yes, you have to leave it for an hour or so.
You have to inflate it on a bike or something.
Like a bike.
What? Like a machine.
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes, it's there.
I had it at home. It was at my parents' house.
Yes, it was at my parents' house. It's at my parents' house.
It's so authentic.
It's a little authentic.
It's JK's way of holding the phone. That's for sure.
It's still this way.
How do you hold it?
It's definitely a shape.It's definitely a shape.
What do you think? What do you think, gentlemen?
Maybe we're all the same.
Like this. Yes, indeed. Look closely.
My hands are small, so I'm a little bit in front.
The one you see a lot.
Surely.
Now, with your finger, one hand like this.
Oh.
Rei-chan.
See?
Just like this.
I wonder what's so girly about Ten-chan.
Maybe she had her fingers open.
Maybe. Like this. Ah, she's a gyaru. Oh, she's a gyaru? She's a gyaru, right? She's got her fingers open, doesn't she? Maybe. Like this.
Oh, it's a gal!
Guys!
I wanna do it!
I don't think so.
But it's so much easier this way.
I'm holding it up with my pinky.
LOL!
Doo-doo-doo!
That's cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
You've all had it.
How do you guys do it?
It's hard to explain.
This is the day...This is the day...
This is hard to explain.
I'm crying, too.
I'm not crying anymore.
I want to eat Renner's bread.
I want to give him bread.
Make me a croissant.
Make croissants. It's hard, isn't it? Difficult.
That's what you mean.
But that's it.
The bread is going to go.
What's wrong?
It's easy.
I was going to cut it up, but I stopped.
I quit.
Let's make it.
I heard it's hard to make.
Heh.
Squeak.
I've made something with rice flour before.
Wow, wow, wow.
It was really difficult, and it turned out really dry. Oh, yeah. I've made it with rice flour before. Wow, that's amazing. It was so difficult and it turned out so dry.
Rice flour was difficult.
I had an image of it being glutinous.
That's true.
But I think a professional is the best for bread.
Really?
But freshly baked bread tastes good.
Oh, that's true.
That's for sure.Indeed.
Smells good, doesn't it?
Do cat ears.
Nyakomiya.
Cat meow.
Meow. Cat. Cat ears? Cat ears?
Cat.
Cat ear?
Cat ears?
cat ears?
Cat ears? Cat ears? Which one is it? It was so fast, so fast.
I didn't see much of it.
I was so surprised.
What day is today?
Oh, it's Thursday.
It's Thursday because I parked at Akiko's navigator.
That's right.
I was hypnotized or something.
That's true.
You know, Nenu-chan, you know how to make bread and that kind of thing?
You know, you can do that on YouTube. Oh, sure. Do you want to do it with me?
Sure. Well, I'm going to go eat. I want to go eat.
We'll all go out to eat. That's for sure.We all go out to eat together. Certainly.
Can we do something like that? Certainly.
Just in time for the TURN CAFE.
Good.
There's something about Parisian cafes.
Bread parfait?
Yes, in Paris.
Restaurants definitely have bread.
It's so good.
Wasn't the bread good?
It was delicious.
You know, the manager, he wanted to get me another loaf,
I don't know,
Oh! What was it? Like a bakery.
He was eating so much.
Yes, a bakery.
Bread,
He wanted to ask for a loaf of bread,
Bakery,
Bakery Breeze?
Give me a bakery.
Bakery? Something like that. What was your reaction? I don't even know what a bakery is! Give me a bakery?
What was the reaction?
Everyone.
Mr. Payá!
Where is it?
You know, when it rained.
It rained.
The wind split us.
It rained so much.It rained like crazy.
It was fun.
It was fun, it really is a memory.
Master was shish-shishing soy sauce the whole time, wasn't he?
Oh, he was.
I heard the soy sauce was really good,
Akima and I would do it all the time.
He was eating soy sauce all the time.
Oh, yeah...
If I ate something, they would take it away from me,
That's all. But Akima-chan, she can definitely lower it. That's why.
But Akiho, you can never be lowered.
I'm going to make this even more difficult.
Until the end.
Asoshimi's part?
Soy sauce.
Wow.
Isn't it tasty?
It was a little sweet.
Like maki shi sushi.
It was delicious.
Soy sauce tastes different.
It depends on the region.
Today is my 20th birthday.
Happy birthday.
Though the women are backing down.
I'm sure they are.
Be 20.
Enjoy your 20s, everyone. I love my birthday.Enjoy your 20's everyone. I love my birthday.
Coming soon.
For sure.
Or...or...or...
Eighteen.
Third year.
You're a junior.
Congratulations.
You're a senior in high school?
I'm a little scared.
It's a little scary.
The voices have started.
We waved our hands at each other.
I'm sorry.
Happy 52nd birthday.
Happy birthday to you. Congratulations on your 52nd birthday. Congratulations on your 52nd birthday.
Congratulations on your 52nd birthday.
Congratulations.
Wait, it's been 50 minutes.
It's true.
That was fast.
I wish I could stop time.
I'm sure you can do it, Mr. Hanyu.
I was the one who was supposed to stop time with the drone.
I'm going to stop the magic.
Here I go.
This is it.Oh, this.
What's going on?
Everyone stopped for a while, didn't they?
This one.
I mean, they did stop, didn't they?
What's going on?
It was a strange time.
That's great.
I didn't stop to comment.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to look like this.
Oh, my God.
It's huge.
What are you guys, anyway?
Cab skills?
I was an infinity day bag.
That's right.
How was it?
It was delicious.
There was nothing.
Cream.
What did you see?
Your hair was cute.
I'm sure it was.
First time. Bear.
I don't have any fire stuff.
Only the book ones?
Normal type.
What about you, Leyanne?What about you, Leyanne?
I was prescient, wasn't I?
Oh!
Foreknowledge.
Precognition
Foreknowledge
Where's Tenchan?
Well, I...
When I say "follow each other," you pull at the worst possible time. Well, I'm the set that went out with you.
Psychedelic?
Yeah, psychedelic.
Stop that thing.
Float it, like, in midair.
He said five minutes.
Oh, shit.
I knew you were serious.
I want you to dress up for Halloween.
Oh, you want to do Halloween?
Don't you guys want to do it?
I want to do it.
I want to have a party.
Oh, sure, I'd like to do something like that.
Don't you want to have a party?
Let's have a party.
We could do it live, you know, like a live broadcast.
It would be nice if we could do something together.
I want Ten-chan to make something with pumpkin.
Pumpkin soup.Pumpkin soup.
Oh, really.
Pumpkin soup.
I want to make it.
I want you to make pumpkin soup.
We can have it together. That's for sure.
Sounds fun.
It's fun.
Maybe it's psychokinisis?
Maybe.
Is that what you call it?
It's also called psychokinisis.
Yes, it is.
Speaking of Halloween, everyone.
Have you seen it?
I really like Kirako's USJ. Oh, that? Huh? It's the one where Kiro is with someone other than a member.
It's the kind of thing that makes me giggle when Kiro is with non-members.
Kiro-chan must have tried her best to talk to them alone.
I'm sure Kilo did his best to talk to her.
I was so happy.
She was so cute.
You saw it, right?
I'm so happy.
It's nice, isn't it?
Oh, Halloween... Matty Mane...
Howdy!
What? The year is ending... yes, when Halloween comes, I'll definitely join the Christmas party.
Oh, I want to attend too! Christmas party! I think I'll go too.
Oh, I want to go! I want to go!
I really want to go. I'd love to.Really. By all means.
Let's go, all of us. I want to go.
I want to do it. I want to do it.
I want to do it.
I want to do it. Oh, no.
Really.
It depends on the year.
I wonder if there is such a thing before Halloween?
I thought so.
I guess so.
Once?
For how many days?
I don't know.
Oh, no?
31 days.
Thirty-one days.
31st.
But really, the day after tomorrow, it will be renewed.
That's right.
I was happy to be able to bring you a lot of the charm of Shinsekai.
Yes, I was. I was happy.
It must have been a fresh experience for you to come here at night.
And this is it, isn't it?
Isn't it forbidden to take pictures of this tree where we are?
Yes, it is. No photography allowed.
If you've never been here before, you should definitely see it.
I think it's very valuable, isn't it?
Yes, it is precious.
Huh, two minutes left.
I see.I see.
That's fast!
That's a lot of hot air!
I hope you enjoyed it.
How did you like it?
Let's get closer to the screen.
It's true, we're all in it together.
It's like a screentime.
Indeed.
Close. Nice.
Is it nice?
A little higher.
There you go.
It looks good.
It's amazing.
It looks like Ocellon.
I'm so happy.
How are you? Buzzy's.
How are you? I miss you.
I'd like to see you soon, wouldn't you?
I miss you.
When was the last time you saw me? Last time.
But, it's Muguri.
I think it's been a while. Tour.
Tour?
Like summer festivals.
Festivals.
But really quite a bit. I don't want to leave Rockin' or the Cafe.
I'd love to see you.I would love to see you.
The seventh single will also be released, so watch chestnuts, everyone,
Let's meet.
Let's wait.
I don't want to see you.
Is this the last time you'll see me? Is this the last time you'll see them?
It's the last one.
Congratulations.
I'll get in line.
I don't know.
It's okay. I want to do it.
Even if it's just for fun.
I want to say have fun.
To everyone.
I'm looking forward to the live show.
I'm going to do my best at the live show, too. That's right. Let's have fun.
Let's do our best.
It's been a while. We're going to do it for the first time.
That's true. So you're used to doing solo gigs?
Yeah.
Yes, it has.
I'm really psyched. Let's go for it!
I'll do my best!
Yes, I will. Well then.
Thank you all for your time.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Please continue to take good care of Sakurazaka, which is filled with so much charm.
Perhaps, Mizuho is already looking forward to working with you.Maybe Mizuho has already taken care of it, thank you.
See the showroom tomorrow.
I definitely have to see it now.
9:00 p.m. is fine.
9:00 p.m. I'll be there at 9:00 p.m. Thank you very much.
So, that's all for now, with Honoho Tamura,
Mizuho Tamura, and,
Rena Moriya,
Rena Moriya, and Tento Yamazaki,
and Tenno Yamazaki, and the art of the blue sky.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
See you soon.
See you on YouTube.
Bye bye.
See you soon.
Bye-bye.
Wait, wait.
Oh no.
Look at me